Ellesia Jessana Janto

Junior Web Developer

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a highly motivated young professional, with international experience in both Europe and the United States. I have a passion for web-development, languages and client facing roles. I posses strong communication skills, from years of customer-facing roles. I am currently searching for a challenging role in a fast-paced work environment.

CONTACT

jantoellesia@gmail.com +14084976077 GitHub: @ellesia12 LinkedIn: @ellesiajanto Portuguese & American

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.js
- SQL/NoSQL
- UX/UI Fundamentals
- SEO (developers)
- SPSS
- R,
- SAP
- Microsoft Office

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

WBS Coding School

August 2020 - December 2020

Bachelor of Science in International Business; Supply Chain & Logistics

Milwaukee School of Engineering

August 2015 - May 2019 GPA 3.72

Bachelor of Science in Industrial Engineering

University of Applied Sciences Lübeck

September 2017 - July 2018

GPA 3.73

International Exchange Program, Germany

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English: Native
- Spanish: Native
- German: Intermediate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kindergarten Teacher

Kita Kinderzimmer | Hamburg, Germany | August 2019 - July 2020

- Managed chaotic situations daily while multi-tasking, focusing on both communication and writing technical reports
- Responsible for the well-being and development of the English language
- Mediating conflict between the children
- Planning, organizing and leading education lessons
- Prepared detailed outlines regarding the educational development of the children

Customer Service Associate

Marriott International Hotels | September 2016 - May 2019

- provide administrative support for all departments, sales, customer service and customer relationship management
- assisting clients with a wide range of transactions, resolving customer issues and handling customer satisfaction
- supporting managers to deliver KPI's as set by the management team
- contribution to the new customer stisfaction survey

Website Design Intern

Peninsula Infiniti | Redwood City, CA | Summer 2017

- updating and editing the company's website in an aesthetically pleasing way by using HTML and CSS code
- collaboration with the marketing team to tailor the website according to their research, and contributing to the creation of wireframes